fantasyalarm.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy - FantasyAlarm.com

## FA Media, LLC Privacy Policy

FA Media, LLC. ("FA") operates, and FantasyAlarm.com owns, the Internet Web site located at www.FantasyAlarm.com (the "FA Web Site" or the "Site"). FA has implemented those Principles in this Privacy Policy, which describes how we collect, use and share identifiable personal information ("INFO"-- your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number or credit card number) we obtain from users of our Site. This Privacy Policy applies to the services offered by FA, including the FA Web site, the FA mobile services, and any other features, content, or applications offered from time to time by FA in connection with the FA Web site (collectively, the "Services").

**The FA Web Site is a general audience site, and FA does not knowingly collect INFO from children under 13 years of age**.  From time to time FA may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our INFO collection and use practices, the features of the Services, or technology. Your continued use of the Services after FA posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. If FA materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your INFO, your INFO will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of and have not objected to the change.

FA makes forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

###   **TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR ALL FA PRODUCTS**

All products and services provided on the FA website whether free or purchased are created with our best efforts for quality and timeliness. All products and services are provided "as-is". FA does not warranty any of the services or products and there is no guarantee for the delivery of any part of the product or service provided whether it is free or paid. By signing up for an account on the FA website you agree that FA Media LLC is not liable for any defects, lost profits, or any damages that may result from defects of any kind. Additionally, you agree that you are the sole owner of the e-mail address which you are registering. You agree that by registering with FA, you may receive messages from FA for third party products and services that are complimentary. We will not provide your e-mail address or information to anyone and your information will be protected by the Privacy Policy below. 

###   **CANCELLATION POLICIES**

#### Subscription Products 

All subscription products purchased on the FA website can be cancelled at anytime. Playbook Pro customers are responsible for monthly payments until cancelling their account. Customers can easily cancel after Log in. If you are on a desktop or laptop, make sure you are logged in, go to the FA homepage, click on Manage Account and then Manage Playbook. If you are on your phone or other mobile device, make sure you are logged in and click on Manage My Playbook Subscription. If at any time, you are not sure how to do anything on our site including cancellation of a subscription product or service, we have customer service on call for you at [support@fantasyalarm.com](mailto:support@fantasyalarm.com). Upon cancellation the account will remain active for 30 days from your last payment date. FA makes it simple to cancel any subscription. 

#### Content Products & Services 

All products and services provided on the FA website are created with our best efforts for quality and timeliness. FA sells content products and access to experts on the FA website. FA believes that our products have high value but will on a case-by-case basis determine whether a refund is appropriate for users who request a refund. To request a refund for a pay product or service, please write to [support@fantasyalarm.com](mailto:support@fantasyalarm.com). 

#### FREE Products & Services 

All products and services provided on the FA website are created with our best efforts for quality and timeliness. FA has FREE products Forums where FA requires a registered account in order to save information on your behalf to make the products better for you and/or the community. If for some reason, you do not wish to be in our community any longer, you may simply request to have yourself removed from our system by writing to [support@fantasyalarm.com](mailto:support@fantasyalarm.com). We will remove you immediately. 

#### Using Promotional Codes for Discounts

FA offers promotional codes (promo codes) for discounted purchases or membership plans. These promo codes MUST be input AFTER the user creates a new account or logs into an existing account. It is the users' responsbility to press the APPLY button and be sure that the promo code has registered for the discounted purchase or subscription. In many instances, FA has no ability to correct product purchase prices or membership sign ups at the wrong prices. For more information you can write to [support@fantasyalarm.com](mailto:support@fantasyalarm.com). 

###   **HOW FA USES THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?**

#### E-mail & Text Notification

We may use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about new services,  recommended services, special offers we think you'll find valuable and important functionality changes to the web site. If you would rather not receive this information, or would like to opt-out of any other information request or distribution, simply submit such a request to us at [support@fantasyalarm.com](mailto:support@fantasyalarm.com). Members may also receive electronic newsletters from FA and or its partners or paid advertisers.  If you would rather not receive any of these newsletters, you may click on the link at the end of the newsletter, or notify us at [support@fantasyalarm.com](mailto:support@fantasyalarm.com).  **FA will never  sell the email addresses or phone numbers of its users to third parties.**

#### Disclosure to Third Parties

Subject to your express opt-in approval, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties, including telemarketers and e-commerce partners, who assist FA. by providing services to users of FA.  We also may share your personally identifiable information at any time if compelled to do so in order to comply with any applicable law or valid legal process. 

Should you change your mind about the information you've provided to us or should your information change, we have provided a way for you to correct, update or remove the personal information you gave us. You can do this simply by contacting us at [support@fantasyalarm.com](mailto:support@fantasyalarm.com).

#### Collection of INFO by FA.

General. When FA collects INFO from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the INFO to us in order to register for the FA Web site. FA may also collect INFO from you if you choose to participate in FA's activities like sweepstakes, contests, games, and surveys, or because you want us to furnish you with products, services, newsletters, or information or in connection with content or suggestions you submit to FA for review. Required registration INFO includes first name, last name, email address, screen name, country, zip and date of birth. Phone number and mailing address are optional _ **.**_ **** We may also obtain INFO from reputable third parties. 

In addition, FA collects other non-INFO including IP address, aggregate user data, and browser type. This data is used to manage and improve the Services, track usage, and for security and monitoring purposes.

Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that FA places on your computer. FA uses the cookies to identify your Internet browser, store users' preferences, and to determine whether you have installed the enabling software needed to access certain material on the Services.

Third party advertisements displayed on the Services may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers. FA does not control these cookies and users of the Services should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. See the "Notice" section below for more information on third party advertising. FA may use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of our Site to INFO obtained from you or a reputable third party. For example, if you've asked us to provide you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on the FA Web site may allow us to limit the materials we provide you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences. However, if FA wishes to combine your personal and cookie or click stream information in this manner, we will obtain your express affirmative consent You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, block third party cookies, or block all cookies. However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to certain features on the Services.

#### FA will provide you with notice about it's info collection practices

When you voluntarily provide INFO to FA, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses FA will make of the information. At the time you provide your INFO, FA will notify you of your options regarding our use of your INFO. (See "Choice" below). Except as described in this Privacy Policy, FA will not share your INFO with third parties unless you have given FA permission to do so. (See "Use" below).

The Services may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with the FA logo or an affiliated entity, even though they are not operated or maintained by FA (for example, co-sponsored chat pages, or advertising sponsor pages). The Site may also carry advertisements from other companies. FA is not responsible for the privacy practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to or integrated with the Services or for the privacy practices of third parties or Internet advertising companies. Once you've left the Services via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third parties or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any INFO they collect from you.  The Services may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with FA visitors to those affiliated sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy.

Some of the advertisements that appear on the Site are delivered to you by third party Internet advertising companies. These companies utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to or use of our Services, including information about the ads they display, via a cookie placed on your computer that reads your IP address. To opt out of information collection by these companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit:

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

#### FA will provide you with choices about the use of your INFO

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, FA will not use the INFO you provide to us for purposes different from the purpose for which it was submitted, or share your INFO with third parties that are not affiliated with FA (i.e., not part of the News America Group) without your permission.

#### FA'S use of INFO

FA will only use the INFO you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If FA obtains INFO from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is also governed by this Privacy Policy.

If you have consented to receive promotional materials from FA, FA may periodically use your email address to send you notifications related to the Services. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from FA, you can change your settings by visiting www.FantasyAlarm.com (must be logged in). You can also click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each promotional email or email [support@fantasyalarm.com](mailto:support@fantasyalarm.com).

FA may share your INFO with companies that are affiliated with us, that is, are part of the News America Group of companies or with FA's co-branded partners. We will not share your credit card information with third parties except those FA uses to perform tasks (such as order fulfillment and payment processing) required to complete purchases you make through the Site. FA employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your INFO. FA may share your INFO with outside contractors, agents, or sponsors who help us manage our information activities (i.e., message boards, sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses, data processing), or with outside contractors, agents, or sponsors who help us with administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contest, promotions, and sweepstakes. These outside contractors may only use your INFO to provide FA with a specific service and not for any other purpose without your consent. FA may also provide your INFO to a third party in those instances where you have chosen to receive certain information and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your INFO.

As described in the "Notice" section above, FA may customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on the Site, or may work with outside companies to do so. Your non-INFO may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. FA prohibits these companies from sharing your information with any third party or from using it for any other purpose other than targeting advertising on the Site.

FA may aggregate INFO and use it anonymously. Anonymous click stream, number of page views calculated by web beacons, and aggregated demographic information may also be shared with FA's advertisers and business partners.

There may be instances when FA may access or disclose INFO or non-INFO without providing you with a choice in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights of FA, other companies within the News America Group or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) to protect the safety and security of users of the Services or members of the public, including acting in urgent circumstances; (iii) to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if FA sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, FA may transfer your INFO to a third party as part of that transaction.

#### FA protects your security of INFO

FA uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard INFO in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, FA uses reasonable methods to make sure that INFO is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.

#### Access, Remedies and Compliance: How to access, Correct or Change your preferences regarding your INFO and how to contact FA about privacy concerns

 Whenever possible, FA Members (people who have registered with FA) may review the INFO that they have provided to us. We will take reasonable steps to correct any INFO a Member informs us is incorrect. If you are a Member, you can view your INFO and Member preferences and profile by accessing www.FantasyAlarm.com (must be logged in).

 If you would like to communicate with us about this Privacy Policy or FA's collection and use of your INFO, to review or correct your INFO, or to stop all future communication from us, please contact FA at: [support@fantasyalarm.com](mailto:support@fantasyalarm.com).
